Here is our car.py file.
这是我们的car.py文件
Let's take a look at the code in here line by line.
让我们来逐行看看这里的代码
First, you'll note the things in red,
首先 你会注意到红色的东西
which are just comments that describe the class.
只是描述类的注释
It describes what the class does and what attributes it has,
它描述了类的定义及其属性
and comments like these are good practice especially
还有一些评论 例如这些是很好的做法 尤其是
if you want your code to be understood by other developers.
如果你希望其他开发人员能够理解你的代码时
Now, if we scroll down a bit,
现在 如果我们向下滚动一下
one of the first things you see is our class car.
你看到的第一个对象就是我们的类 汽车
This looks a bit like a function declaration,
这看起来有点像函数声明
but the word class let's Python know that the code that
但是这个词‘类’让 Python 知道后面那个代码
follows should describe the state and functionality of a car object.
应描述汽车对象的状态和功能
Objects are also always capitalized,
对象同样应始终大写
and so, we see that Car is capitalized here.
所以我们看到 Car 是大写的
Next, we see the init function which is responsible for
接下来 我们看到初始函数
creating space in memory to make a specific car object like Carlat.
它负责在内存中创建一个特定的汽车对象 如 Carlat
So when you run code like Car.Car and pass in some initial parameters,
所以当你运行像 Car.Car 这样的代码并输入一些初始参数时
this is the function that's called.
这就是所调用的函数
This is where the initial state is created from
这就是从输入的位置和速度变量
the position and velocity variables that are passed in.
所创建的初始状态的位置
We also see variables for the cars world,
我们还可以看到相对于汽车的变量 包括世界
its color and its path.
及其颜色和路径
We know the world is just a 2D grid.
我们知道世界只是一个二维网格
The color will revisit, but for now, no,
我们会重新考虑颜色 不过不是现在
that's why our car appears red in our grid,
这就是为什么车在网格中显示为红色的原因
and the path is just going to be a list of
路径只是一个汽车行驶过的位置列表
locations that a car has visited that we can then visualize.
我们可以将其可视化
So the most important lines of code in here are the state and the world,
所以这里最重要的代码是状态和世界
and all of the variables in here are something that a car object keeps track of.
这里的所有变量都是汽车对象所跟踪的
Next, if we scroll down is the move function.
接下来 如果我们向下滚动 则是滚动函数
The description says the move function moves the car in
它的描述为 滚动函数使汽车沿着
the direction of the velocity and updates the state,
速率方向运动并更新其状态
and this may look familiar from our predict state function.
这看起来像预测状态函数
Move uses a constant velocity model to move the car
滚动函数采用一个恒定速率模型
in the direction of its velocity vy and vx,
在其速率 VY 和 VX 方向移动汽车
and if we look at one portion of this equation,
如果我们看这个方程的一部分
we can see that it's our constant velocity model.
我们可以看到这是我们的恒定速率模型
It says y, our initial position,
它说我们的初始位置 y
plus our y velocity times are change in time becomes our new predictive position,
加上时间与 y 速度的乘积 成为了我们新预测的位置
and at the end, we update the current state variable that was initialized in an int.
最后 我们更新在 int 中初始化的当前状态变量
And this is how we track the state of the car as we move.
这就是我们在运动时跟踪汽车状态的方式
Next, we see our Turn left function,
接下来 我们来看左转函数
which simply rotates the velocity values to the left,
它将速度值简单地向左旋转
and this function updates our state again with the new velocity, and finally,
这个函数采用新的速度再次更新汽车的状态 最后
at the end, we have this display world function,
我们得到了这个显示世界的函数
which you shouldn't change, but feel free to read.
你不能改变 但可以随意阅读
This is responsible for display in a grid world and our car within it,
它负责在一个网格中显示世界以及我们的车在其中的位置
and it uses pyplot for visualization.
并且它使用 pyplot 来进行可视化
Next, it will be up to you to read through this code,
接下来 由你来阅读这段代码
understand how a car object like Carlat tracks down state,
了解 Carlat 等汽车对象如何跟踪状态
and together, it will help write some additional functions within this car class.
这些一起 可以帮助你在这个汽车类中写一些额外的函数